[{"question": " okay, she is the star of the play. and she is my girlfriend! i get to have sex with the star of the play!", "answer": " people can hear you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 1, "asentId": 2}, {"question": " wow! she looks great. doesn\u0092t she?", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 5, "asentId": 6}, {"question": " hi!", "answer": " hi!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 7, "asentId": 8}, {"question": " that is one good looking man!", "answer": " is it just me, or can you actually see his abs through his overcoat?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 9, "asentId": 10}, {"question": " sooo, you\u0092ve been doing this long?", "answer": " no, you\u0092re my first. put the money on the table.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 11, "asentId": 12}, {"question": " dude!", "answer": " is that an expensive blouse?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 15, "asentId": 16}, {"question": " oh, hey, mon, do you still have your like old blouses and dresses from high school?", "answer": " yeah, i think i have some around here somewhere. why?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 21, "asentId": 22}, {"question": " hey, rach! i made a pile of your stuff over on this side of the room. if you could just\u009a\u009athrow your purses at", "answer": " bloomingdale\u0092s eliminated my department.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 25, "asentId": 26}, {"question": " oh my god, are you out of a job?", "answer": " no, but they stuck me in personal shopping. which is just a huge step down!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 27, "asentId": 28}, {"question": " personal shopping? what is that? like where you walk around with snooty rich people and tell them what to buy?", "answer": " uh-huh.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 29, "asentId": 30}, {"question": " that sounds great!", "answer": "  hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 31, "asentId": 32}, {"question": " umm, excuse me, we switched apartments. you can\u0092t eat are food anymore, that-that gravy train had ended.", "answer": "  there\u0092s gravy?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 33, "asentId": 34}, {"question": " what are you doing?", "answer": " i think i left a donut up here.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 37, "asentId": 38}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 39, "asentId": 40}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " ooh! how was kathy\u0092s play?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 41, "asentId": 42}, {"question": " well, kathy gets half-naked and simulates sex with a real good lookin\u0092 guy.", "answer": " yeah, it\u0092s like someone literally wrote down my worst nightmare and then charged me $32 to see it!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 43, "asentId": 44}, {"question": " that\u0092s a good idea for a business!", "answer": " i\u0092m totally screwed. okay, they are gonna be hot and heavy on stage every night, and then they\u0092re gonna go to their cast parties and he\u0092s gonna try to undermine me. y'know it\u0092ll be like, \"so where\u0092s your boyfriend, what\u0092s-his-name, chester?\" and she\u0092ll go, \"no-no-no, it\u0092s chandler.\" and he\u0092ll go, \"whatever. ha-ha-ha-ha!\"", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 45, "asentId": 46}, {"question": "  that-that is a good trick.", "answer": " all right, look, look, what am i gonna do?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 47, "asentId": 48}, {"question": " chandler, look they\u0092re actors. they\u0092re there to do a job, just \u0091cause they work together, doesn\u0092t mean they\u0092re gonna get together. i mean just \u0091cause it happened with susan sarandon and tim robbins, it doesn\u0092t mean it\u0092s gonna happen with them.", "answer": " oh-oh, alec baldwin and kim basinger.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 49, "asentId": 50}, {"question": " tom cruise and nicole kidman.", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 51, "asentId": 52}, {"question": " hey, mel gibson and clint eastwood.", "answer": " they\u0092re not a couple!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 53, "asentId": 54}, {"question": " oh-okay, i get the game now.", "answer": " okay look, look, let me ask you a question, when they were doing it on stage, was it like really hot?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 55, "asentId": 56}, {"question": " oh yeah!", "answer": " well okay, so then you\u0092re fine. the rule is when two actors are actually doing it off-stage all the sexual tension between them is gone. okay? so as long as it\u0092s hot onstage you got nothing to worry about. it\u0092s when the heat goes away, that\u0092s when you\u0092re in trouble.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 57, "asentId": 58}, {"question": " really?", "answer": " look, you guys have been to every play i\u0092ve ever been in, have i ever had chemistry on stage?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 59, "asentId": 60}, {"question": " no.", "answer": " noooo!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 61, "asentId": 62}, {"question": " so uh, man, are you gonna go to the play with me tonight?", "answer": " y\u0092know what, i don\u0092t know how comfortable i am going to see how hot the sex is between some guy and your girlfriend.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 63, "asentId": 64}, {"question": " yeah, i know but\u009a", "answer": " oh no-no-no, i\u0092m there.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 65, "asentId": 66}, {"question": "  hey!", "answer": " hey mon! want some pancakes?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 67, "asentId": 68}, {"question": " you made pancakes?", "answer": " yep! grab a plate.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 69, "asentId": 70}, {"question": " no-no, stay right there.  gettin\u0092 closer.", "answer": " okay, okay, but don\u0092t worry, because we also have cereals, muffins, waffles, and, jams, jellies, and marmalades. which i\u0092m fairly certain are the same thing.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 73, "asentId": 74}, {"question": " listen also we\u0092re uh, we\u0092re watching the game here saturday night, if people want to come over.", "answer": " oh yeah!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 75, "asentId": 76}, {"question": " oh, i was thinking about having people over for the game.", "answer": " oh yeah, who\u0092s playing?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 77, "asentId": 78}, {"question": " the players.", "answer": " somebody seems to be missing being the hostess.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 79, "asentId": 80}, {"question": "  please, it\u0092s a relief is what it is, is what it is.", "answer": " all right pheebs, stick out your plate!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 81, "asentId": 82}, {"question": "  monica, i\u0092m quitting! i just helped an 81 year old woman put on a thong and she didn\u0092t even buy it!  i\u0092m telling you i\u0092m quitting! that\u0092s it! i\u0092m talking to my boss right now!  yes i am!  yes i am! yes i am! yes i am! yes i am! yes i am! okay bye, call me when you get this message.  oh! mr. waltham, i ah really need to talk to you.", "answer": " in a moment, please, i\u0092m in the middle of a task. and you have a customer.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 85, "asentId": 86}, {"question": " hi!", "answer": " hi, i\u0092m joshua.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 87, "asentId": 88}, {"question": " hi, i\u0092m rachel green. what can i do for you joshua?", "answer": " well, i need a whole new wardrobe. my wife, well my ex-wife\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 89, "asentId": 90}, {"question": " anyway, she burned all of my clothes. i got away with two things. this suit and what turned out to be a skirt.", "answer": " well, at least that\u0092s a great suit.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 93, "asentId": 94}, {"question": " yeah, but it wasn\u0092t much fun dropping it off at the dry cleaners in the skirt.  so i need everything down to underwear, so if you\u0092re willing, i\u0092m all yours.", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 95, "asentId": 96}, {"question": " rachel, you needed to speak to me?", "answer": " no-no, that wasn\u0092t me!  well, we should get started. let me show you my underwear.  the selection of underwear we carry.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 97, "asentId": 98}, {"question": " i\u0092m right! right? there was like no chemistry between them. before they had heat, and now there\u0092s no heat! now you know what this means, joey told us what this means!", "answer": " all right, let\u0092s not jump to any conclusions. all right? there was some sexual chemistry between them.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 103, "asentId": 104}, {"question": " come on, it was like cousins having sex up there!", "answer": " here she comes. don\u0092t say a word, okay? just be cool, don\u0092t be\u009ay'know you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 105, "asentId": 106}, {"question": " hey you guys!", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 107, "asentId": 108}, {"question": " hi!  thank you so much for coming again. did you like it tonight?", "answer": " oh, absolutely!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 109, "asentId": 110}, {"question": " oh, i loved the play. you were great, and nick ditto. clearly you\u0092re having sex with him.", "answer": " okay, i\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 115, "asentId": 116}, {"question": " clearly, i\u0092m having sex with him?", "answer": " oh come on, it was so obvious! there was no chemistry between you two!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 117, "asentId": 118}, {"question": " okay, so let me just get this straight. you\u0092re accusing me of cheating on you, and insulting my performance?", "answer": " y\u0092know, i-i could see how this could happen, y'know you\u0092re up there every night, you\u0092re naked, touching, kissing.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 119, "asentId": 120}, {"question": " acting! chandler, this is my job! i\u0092m-i\u0092m playing a part in a play! how can you not trust me?!", "answer": " well, you can understand, given how we started.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 121, "asentId": 122}, {"question": " oh, wow. i can\u0092t believe you\u0092re throwing that in my face.", "answer": " well, that is what happened, and i don\u0092t even see you denying this!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 123, "asentId": 124}, {"question": " i\u0092ll tell you what, chandler, why don\u0092t you call me when you grow up!", "answer": " yeah, well, don\u0092t expect that to happen anytime soon! commercial break", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 125, "asentId": 126}, {"question": " i have the best job in the entire world! the most adorable guy came over today, and i got to dress him up all day!", "answer": " rachel has a new doll.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 127, "asentId": 128}, {"question": " oh, i wish he was a doll, then i could get a rachel doll and bump them together and make kissy noises. oh! and he has the most beautiful name, i never realised it, joshua! josh-u-a! joshua! josh.", "answer": " uh, hello!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 129, "asentId": 130}, {"question": " hi-e!!", "answer": " ooh, what do i smell?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 131, "asentId": 132}, {"question": " fresh cookies! hot from the oven!", "answer": " ooh!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 135, "asentId": 136}, {"question": " please, have some!", "answer": " oh, yumm!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 137, "asentId": 138}, {"question": " yeah, i\u0092ve just been fiddling around in here making delicious treats for everyone.", "answer": "  wow! the new playboy!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 139, "asentId": 140}, {"question": " yeah, it\u0092s just something i picked up.", "answer": " cookies and porn, you\u0092re the best mom ever!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 141, "asentId": 142}, {"question": " what? what?", "answer": " well, it was just something josh said about v-necks, but you had to be there.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 143, "asentId": 144}, {"question": " yeah, how does jason look in a v-neck?", "answer": " it\u0092s joshua.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 145, "asentId": 146}, {"question": " wait! wait! this isn\u0092t take-out!", "answer": "  well, i hate to eat and run, but\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 149, "asentId": 150}, {"question": " no, wait, please don\u0092t go! i\u0092ve got porn for you too!", "answer": " yeah, i don\u0092t need it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 151, "asentId": 152}, {"question": " people are supposed to wanna hang out here!", "answer": " why? honey, what is the big deal?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 153, "asentId": 154}, {"question": " i\u0092m the hostess! not those guys! i\u0092m always the hostess! i mean, i was always the hostess, i mean even when i was little, i mean the girls brought their dollies to my tea party, i-i served the best air.", "answer": " well, why did you make like a whole big thing out of y'know, everyone has to hang out in the big apartment?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 155, "asentId": 156}, {"question": " \u0091cause they took our apartment, i wanted to punish them. but i\u0092m-i\u0092m done now. they\u0092ve suffered enough.", "answer": " if you wanted to punish them, you should\u0092ve just made them hang out here!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 157, "asentId": 158}, {"question": " yeah, that\u0092s true.", "answer": " all right then, when i\u0092m done with this place, it\u0092s gonna be ten times better than that place!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 159, "asentId": 160}, {"question": " steps!  slut!  you will all be very happy to hear that kathy is sleeping with that guy!", "answer": " what?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 163, "asentId": 164}, {"question": " so you were right?", "answer": " i confronted her, and she didn\u0092t deny it!  i don\u0092t live here!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 165, "asentId": 166}, {"question": " chandler!", "answer": " chandler, what did she say?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 167, "asentId": 168}, {"question": " wait a minute.", "answer": " come here.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 169, "asentId": 170}, {"question": " are you sure?", "answer": " well, i may be drunk, but i know what she said! then i went over to beefsteak julie\u0092s\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 171, "asentId": 172}, {"question": " beefsteak charlie\u0092s?", "answer": " yes! see you and i have always been like\u0097", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 173, "asentId": 174}, {"question": " whoops.  oh, hey, do you need help with that?", "answer": " nah, i got it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 175, "asentId": 176}, {"question": " hi!", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 179, "asentId": 180}, {"question": " so i was with joshua for an hour today, and he has not asked me out. it\u0092s just so frustrating!", "answer": " why don\u0092t you ask him out?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 181, "asentId": 182}, {"question": " oh, yeah, totally! that\u0092s such a turn-on!", "answer": " really? it doesn\u0092t seem desperate?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 183, "asentId": 184}, {"question": " oh-ooh, that\u0092s the turn-on.", "answer": " he just got a divorce right?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 185, "asentId": 186}, {"question": " hmm-mmm.", "answer": " so he\u0092s probably really nervous around women, y'know? maybe, you just have to make the first move.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 187, "asentId": 188}, {"question": " yeah but, i\u0092ve never asked a guy out before.", "answer": "  you\u0092ve never asked a guy out?!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 189, "asentId": 190}, {"question": " no. have you?", "answer": " thousands of times!! that doesn\u0092t make me sound too good does it?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 191, "asentId": 192}, {"question": " i don\u0092t even know how i would go about it.", "answer": " oh-oh-oh-oh, how i do it is, i look a woman up and down and say, \"hey, how you doin\u0092?\"", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 193, "asentId": 194}, {"question": " oh, please!", "answer": "  hey, how you doin\u0092?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 195, "asentId": 196}, {"question": " you know what, i\u0092m gonna do that, i\u0092m gonna call him up, and i\u0092m gonna ask him out. i can do that. ask him out.  how you doin\u0092?  hi! joshua? it\u0092s rachel green from bloomingdale\u0092s.  yeah, umm, i was wondering if you umm, if you umm, left your wallet at the store today? well, we found a wallet, and we\u0097 the license? well, that is a good idea! uh, well, let\u0092s see here this says this license belongs to a uh, uh, belongs to a mister uh, pheebs, and umm, yeah, so sorry to bother you at home. i\u0092ll see you tomorrow. bye.   you\u0092ve done that a thousand times?", "answer": " i\u0092ve never done that.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 197, "asentId": 198}, {"question": " ohh, god, i just got so nervous that he would say no.", "answer": " well, you gotta give him something that he can\u0092t say no too. like uh, knicks tickets! invite the guy to a knicks game, you\u0092re guaranteed he\u0092ll say yes!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 199, "asentId": 200}, {"question": " really?! you think that will work?", "answer": " absolutely! and if it doesn\u0092t, can i get the extra ticket?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 201, "asentId": 202}, {"question": " did she call?", "answer": " no, sorry.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 205, "asentId": 206}, {"question": " all right, maybe i should call her.", "answer": " no! forget her, man! you don\u0092t need her, you don\u0092t need that!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 207, "asentId": 208}, {"question": " he\u0092s right, what she did was unforgivable.", "answer": " well, yeah, but y'know, what-what if i was wrong?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 209, "asentId": 210}, {"question": " how might you be wrong?", "answer": " well y'know, what if she didn\u0092t actually sleep with the guy?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 211, "asentId": 212}, {"question": " dude, tell me she actually told you this.", "answer": " she did not have to tell me, i saw the play, and there was no heat. back me up here, ross!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 213, "asentId": 214}, {"question": " that\u0092s all you\u0092re basing this on?", "answer": " that\u0092s not backing me up! look, you said with the off-stage and the heat, and the onstage and the oy heat.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 215, "asentId": 216}, {"question": " whoa-whoa, that-that was just a theory! there\u0092s a lot of theories that didn\u0092t pan out. the lone gunman. communism. geometry.", "answer": " oh my god!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 217, "asentId": 218}, {"question": " what do you think?", "answer": " oh! well, as a single woman, who is available, i think you look great!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 221, "asentId": 222}, {"question": " huh.  yeah?", "answer": " yep. oh, yeah, look you great.  oh yeah. yeah, this looks great.  umm, so you like", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 223, "asentId": 224}, {"question": " i do. i do. i love it. in fact, i think i\u0092m gonna wear it home.", "answer": " great.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 225, "asentId": 226}, {"question": " all right, thank you so much for all your help.", "answer": " sure.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 227, "asentId": 228}, {"question": " well, i guess this is uh, i guess this is it.", "answer": " yeah-eah-ha!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 229, "asentId": 230}, {"question": " thanks.  maybe i\u0092ll see in the spring, with the uh, y\u0092know, for the uh, bathing suits.", "answer": " oh well, you don\u0092t want to do that now?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 231, "asentId": 232}, {"question": " ah, that\u0092s okay, thanks.", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 233, "asentId": 234}, {"question": " basketball!", "answer": "  i\u0092m sorry.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 237, "asentId": 238}, {"question": " i uh, i have two tickets to the knicks game tonight if you\u0092re interested, just as a thank you for this week.", "answer": " wow! that would be great.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 239, "asentId": 240}, {"question": " really?", "answer": " yeah, that would be fantastic! my-my nephew is crazy about the knicks! this is fantastic, thank you so much rachel.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 241, "asentId": 242}, {"question": " good morning.", "answer": " hi!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 243, "asentId": 244}, {"question": "  hey.", "answer": " hey. i just, i just wanted to come over to-to say that i\u0092m sorry. y\u0092know? i know i acted like the biggest idiot in the world, and i can completely understand why you were so upset.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 245, "asentId": 246}, {"question": " oh wow. i really wish you\u0092d call me.", "answer": " yeah, i know, i-i wish i had too, but y\u0092know i-i think this is a good thing. y'know? \u0091cause we\u0092ve had our first fight, and now we can move on. y\u0092know, i know for me\u0097 nick\u0092s pants?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 247, "asentId": 248}, {"question": " yeah.", "answer": " yeah. well, i think our second fight is going to be a big one!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 249, "asentId": 250}, {"question": " okay, for next time, what do you say?", "answer": " i have an extra ticket. an extra ticket. not, two tickets, i have an extra ticket.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 251, "asentId": 252}, {"question": " so the first time you ask a guy out, he-he turns you down?", "answer": " he didn\u0092t turn me down! he\u0092s at the game isn\u0092t he? i got the date, i\u0092m just not on it!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 253, "asentId": 254}, {"question": "  okay, it\u0092s ready. come on.", "answer": " what\u0092s ready?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 255, "asentId": 256}, {"question": " oh my god!", "answer": " wow! monica!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 259, "asentId": 260}, {"question": " great!", "answer": " this is beautiful!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 261, "asentId": 262}, {"question": " oh did you\u0097what did you\u0097did you work for two days straight?", "answer": " pretty much.  so, what do you, what do you think of the floor?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 263, "asentId": 264}, {"question": " i don\u0092t know, it looks the same.", "answer": " you used to have carpet.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 265, "asentId": 266}, {"question": " oh yeah!", "answer": " so i made snacks. please, just hang out okay? i\u0092m just gonna rest my eyes just a little bit.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 267, "asentId": 268}, {"question": " look, mon, do you want us to uh, come back later?", "answer": " oh no-no-no, stay, stay, stay, just keep talking. i\u0092m always the hostess.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 269, "asentId": 270}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " how\u0092d it go?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 271, "asentId": 272}, {"question": " well, she wasn\u0092t sleeping with him.", "answer": " oh good!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 273, "asentId": 274}, {"question": " she is now.", "answer": " what are you saying?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 275, "asentId": 276}, {"question": " i\u0092m saying that she\u009a is a devil woman! y\u0092know i mean you think you know someone and then they turn around and they sleep with nick! nick, with his rock hard pecs, and his giant man-nipples! i hate him, i hate her! well, i don\u0092t hate her, i love her. this is all my fault really.", "answer": " how? how is your fault?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 277, "asentId": 278}, {"question": " because, i-i should\u0092ve called! y\u0092know if i had just called her after our big, stupid fight, she never would\u0092ve gone out with nick, and they would\u0092ve ended up in bed together. i threw her at his man nipples!", "answer": " honey, this is not your fault, just because you guys had a fight, it does not justify her sleeping with someone.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 279, "asentId": 280}, {"question": " rachel, one of your customers seems to have left his billfold. a joshua bergen.", "answer": " really?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 283, "asentId": 284}, {"question": " will you call him?", "answer": " yes! i will! absolutely!  hello, rachel. hi, joshua. i left my wallet here on purpose. really? yes, i just wanted to see you again. oh, i\u0092m glad. rachel, i\u0092d like to say something to you. yes? how you doin\u0092?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep13.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 285, "asentId": 286}]